Guide to the Clarence Prouty Shedd Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Source Material, 1920s-1940s; Series III
  - RSU: Louisiana State University (Box 64, Folder 586)
  - RSU: Maine, University of (Box 64, Folder 587)
  - RSU: Massachusetts, University of (Box 64, Folder 588)
  - RSU: Miami University (Ohio) (Box 64, Folder 589)
  - RSU: Michigan State University (Box 64, Folder 590)
  - RSU: Michigan, University of (Box 64, Folder 591)
  - RSU: Michigan, University of (Box 64, Folder 592)
  - RSU: Michigan, University of (Box 64, Folder 593)
  - RSU: Minnesota, University of (Box 65, Folder 594)
  - RSU: Minnesota, University of (Box 65, Folder 595)
  - RSU: Mississippi State College for Women (Box 65, Folder 596)
  - RSU: Mississippi, University of (Box 65, Folder 597)
  - RSU: Missouri, University of (Box 65, Folder 598)
  - RSU: Montana State College (Box 65, Folder 599)
  - RSU: Montana State University (Box 65, Folder 600)
  - RSU: Nebraska, University of (Box 65, Folder 601)
  - RSU: Nevada, University of (Box 65, Folder 602)
  - RSU: New Hampshire, University of (Box 65, Folder 603)
  - RSU: New Mexico State College (Box 65, Folder 604)
  - RSU: New Mexico, University of (Box 65, Folder 605)
  - RSU: New York State College for Teachers (Box 65, Folder 606)
  - RSU: North Carolina State College (Box 65, Folder 607)
  - RSU: North Carolina, University of (Box 65, Folder 608)
  - RSU: North Carolina, University of (Women's College) (Box 65, Folder 609)
  - RSU: North Dakota, University of (Box 65, Folder 610)
  - RSU: Northwestern University (Box 65, Folder 611)
  - RSU: Ohio State University (Box 66, Folder 612)
  - RSU: Ohio State University (Box 66, Folder 613)
  - RSU: Ohio University (Box 66, Folder 614)
  - RSU: Oklahoma Agricultural and Mechanical College (Box 66, Folder 615)
  - RSU: Oklahoma, University of (Box 66, Folder 616)
  - RSU: Oregon State College (Box 66, Folder 617)
  - RSU: Oregon State College (Box 66, Folder 618)
  - RSU: Oregon, University of (Box 66, Folder 619)
  - RSU: Pendle Hill (Box 67, Folder 620)
  - RSU: Pennsylvania State University (Box 67, Folder 621)
  - RSU: Pennsylvania State University (Box 67, Folder 622)
  - RSU: Pennsylvania State University (Box 67, Folder 623)
  - RSU: Pennsylvania State University (Box 67, Folder 624)
  - RSU: Pennsylvania, University of (Box 67, Folder 625)
  - RSU: Rhode Island, University of (Box 67, Folder 626)
  - RSU: Rutgers University (Box 67, Folder 627)
  - RSU: San Diego State College (Box 67, Folder 628)
  - RSU: South Carolina, University of (Box 67, Folder 629)
  - RSU: South Dakota State College (Box 67, Folder 630)
  - RSU: Tennessee, University of (Box 67, Folder 631)
  - RSU: Texas Agricultural and Mechanical College (Box 68, Folder 632)
  - RSU: Texas Technological College (Box 68, Folder 633)
  - RSU: Texas, University of (Box 68, Folder 634)
  - RSU: Texas Women's University (Box 68, Folder 635)
  - RSU: Utah, University of (Box 68, Folder 636)
  - RSU: Vermont, University of (Box 68, Folder 637)
  - RSU: Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 68, Folder 638)
  - RSU: Virginia, University of (Box 68, Folder 639)
  - RSU: Washburn University of Topeka (Box 68, Folder 640)
  - RSU: Washington State University (Box 68, Folder 641)
  - RSU: Washington University (Box 68, Folder 642)
  - RSU: Washington, University of (Box 68, Folder 643)
  - RSU: Wayne University (Box 68, Folder 644)
  - RSU: West Virginia University (Box 68, Folder 645)
  - RSU: Western Illinois State College (Box 68, Folder 646)
  - RSU: Western Michigan University (Box 68, Folder 647)
  - RSU: Whittier College (Box 68, Folder 648)
  - RSU: Wichita, University of (Box 69, Folder 649)
  - RSU: William and Mary, College of (Box 69, Folder 650)
  - RSU: Winthrop College (Box 69, Folder 651)
  - RSU: Wisconsin, University of (Box 69, Folder 652)
  - RSU: Wisconsin, University of (Box 69, Folder 653)
  - RSU: Wyoming, University of (Box 69, Folder 654)
  - Religious Perspectives in College Teaching (Box 70, Folder 655)
  - Resources and Relationships in Student Work (Box 70, Folder 656)
  - Secularization of Higher Education (Box 70, Folder 657)
  - Southern Baptist Student Work (Box 70, Folder 658)
  - Southern Baptist Student Work (Box 70, Folder 659)
  - Statistics of Higher Education (Box 70, Folder 660)
  - Student Christian Movement (Box 70, Folder 661)
  - Student Christian Movement in Various Countries - (card file) (Box 71, Folder 662)
  - Student Conferences: Estes Park (Box 72, Folder 663)
  - Student Conferences: Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 664)
  - Student Friendship Fund (Box 72, Folder 665)
  - Student Religious Attitudes: Butler Study, 1936 (Box 72, Folder 666)
  - Student Religious Attitudes: Changing Values (Box 72, Folder 667)
  - Student Religious Attitudes: Changing Values (Box 72, Folder 668)
  - Student Religious Attitudes: Changing Values (Box 72, Folder 669)
  - Student Religious Attitudes: Changing Values (Box 73, Folder 670)
  - Student Religious Attitudes: Changing Values (Box 73, Folder 671)
  - Student Religious Attitudes: College Generation of the 1960's (Box 73, Folder 672)
  - Student Religious Attitudes: Surveys (Box 73, Folder 673)
  - Student Volunteer Movement: Miscellaneous (Box 73, Folder 674)
  - Student Volunteer Movement Tenth Quadrennial Convention, Detroit, 1927-28 (Box 73, Folder 675)
  - Student Volunteer Movement Tenth Quadrennial Convention, Detroit, 1927-28 (Box 73, Folder 676)
  - Summer Courses for Leaders of University Religious Work, 1928-1931 Feb (Box 74, Folder 677)
  - Summer Courses for Leaders of University Religious Work, 1931 Mar-1931 Jul (Box 74, Folder 678)
  - Summer Courses for Leaders of University Religious Work, 1931 Aug-1939 (Box 74, Folder 679)
  - Summer Courses for Leaders of University Religious Work, 1940-1948, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 680)
  - Supervision of Student Association Work (Box 74, Folder 681)
  - Supervision of Student Association Work (Box 74, Folder 682)
  - Teaching Methods (Box 74, Folder 683)
  - Teaching Religion (Box 75, Folder 684)
  - Teaching Religion (Box 75, Folder 685)
  - Teaching Religion (Box 75, Folder 686)
  - Transition from High School to College (Box 75, Folder 687)
  - Trends in Higher Education (Box 75, Folder 688)
  - Trends in Higher Education (Box 75, Folder 689)
  - Trends in Higher Education (Box 75, Folder 690)
  - Two Centuries of Student Christian Movements (TCSCM): Abstract of Shedd's dissertation (Box 76, Folder 691)
  - TCSCM: Alabama Polytechnic - Alexandria Theological Seminary Institute (Box 76, Folder 692)
  - TCSCM: Amherst College (Box 76, Folder 693)
  - TCSCM: Andover Theological Seminary (Box 76, Folder 694)
  - TCSCM: Auburn Theological Seminary (Box 76, Folder 695)
  - TCSCM: Beloit College (Box 76, Folder 696)
  - TCSCM: Bibliographies (Box 76, Folder 697)
  - TCSCM: Biographies (Box 76, Folder 698)
  - TCSCM: Bowdoin College (Box 76, Folder 699)
  - TCSCM: Brown University (Box 76, Folder 700)
  - TCSCM:Bucknell University (Box 76, Folder 701)
  - TCSCM: Carthage College (Illinois); Centre College (Kentucky) (Box 76, Folder 702)
  - TCSCM: Colby College (Waterville College); Columbia University; Connecticut Literary Institute (Box 76, Folder 703)
  - TCSCM: Colgate University (Madison University) (Box 76, Folder 704)
  - TCSCM: Cornell College (Iowa); Cornell University (Box 76, Folder 705)
  - TCSCM: Correspondence with libraries (Box 76, Folder 706)
  - TCSCM: Cumberland University (Tennessee) (Box 76, Folder 707)
  - TCSCM: Dartmouth College (Box 76, Folder 708)
  - TCSCM: DePauw University (Box 77, Folder 709)
  - TCSCM: Early Student Religious Societies (Box 77, Folder 710)
  - TCSCM: European letters, 1820's, 1830's (Box 77, Folder 711)
  - TCSCM: Georgia, University of; Gettysburg College; Granville College (Dennison); Grinnell College (Box 77, Folder 712)
  - TCSCM: Hamilton College; Hampden-Sydney College; Hanover College (Box 77, Folder 713)
  - TCSCM: Harvard University (Box 77, Folder 714)
  - TCSCM: Illinois State Normal University; Illinois, University of (Box 77, Folder 715)
  - TCSCM: Jefferson College "Key sentences" Kenyon College (Box 77, Folder 716)
  - TCSCM: Lake Geneva Conferences; Lafayette College; Lenox College (Iowa) (Box 77, Folder 717)
  - TCSCM: McGill University (Box 77, Folder 718)
  - TCSCM: Marion College (Missouri); Maryville College (Tennessee); Massachusetts Historical Society (Box 77, Folder 719)
  - TCSCM: Michigan, University of; includes letters from John R. Mott (Box 77, Folder 720)
  - TCSCM: Middlebury College; Milton College (Wisconsin); Minnesota, University of (Box 77, Folder 721)
  - TCSCM: Mississippi, University of; Morse, Richard C.; correspondence (Box 77, Folder 722)
  - TCSCM: New Brunswick Seminary and Colleg;e New Hampton Lit. and Theol. Institute (Virginia); Newton Theological Institute (Box 77, Folder 723)
  - TCSCM: New College, Edinburgh, Scotland (Box 77, Folder 724)
  - TCSCM: New York Theological Seminary (Box 77, Folder 725)
  - TCSCM: North-Western College; Oberlin College; Otterbein College; Olivet College (Box 77, Folder 726)
  - TCSCM: Peirce Academy; Pennsylvania State College; Pennsylvania, University of (Box 77, Folder 727)
  - TCSCM: Princeton Philadelphian Society (Box 77, Folder 728)
  - TCSCM: Princeton Theological Seminary (Box 78, Folder 729)
  - TCSCM: Publication correspondence (Box 78, Folder 730)
  - TCSCM: Reviews of the book (Box 78, Folder 731)
  - TCSCM: Richmond College; Roanoke College; Rochester Theological Seminary; Rochester, University of (Box 78, Folder 732)
  - TCSCM: Rutgers College (Box 78, Folder 733)
  - TCSCM: South Carolina, University of (Box 78, Folder 734)
  - TCSCM: State student work history (Box 78, Folder 735)
  - TCSCM: State student work history (Box 78, Folder 736)
  - TCSCM: Summer student conferences (Box 78, Folder 737)
  - TCSCM: Tennessee, University of; Toronto, University of (Box 78, Folder 738)
  - TCSCM: Union College (Box 78, Folder 739)
  - TCSCM: Vermont, University of (Box 78, Folder 740)
  - TCSCM: Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 78, Folder 741)
  - TCSCM: Virginia, University of (Box 78, Folder 742)
  - TCSCM: Washington College; Washington and Jefferson College; Washington and Lee University; Washington, University of (Box 78, Folder 743)
  - TCSCM: Weidensall, Robert; correspondence, biographical information (Box 78, Folder 744)
  - TCSCM: Wesleyan University (Connecticut) Western Reserve Academy; Western Theological Seminary William and Mary, College of (Box 78, Folder 745)
  - TCSCM: Williams College (Box 78, Folder 746)
  - TCSCM: Winona State Teacher's College (Box 79, Folder 747)
  - TCSCM: Wisconsin, University of; Wittenberg College (Box 79, Folder 748)
  - TCSCM: Wishard, Luther; notes from scrapbook (Box 79, Folder 749)
  - TCSCM: Yale University (Box 79, Folder 750)
  - TCSCM: Yale University (Box 79, Folder 751)
  - TCSCM: Yale University (Box 79, Folder 752)
  - TCSCM: Y.M.C.A. (Box 79, Folder 753)
  - TCSCM: Chapters l, 2, 3; Early societies (Box 79, Folder 754)
  - TCSCM: Chapter 2 (Box 79, Folder 755)
  - TCSCM: Chapters 2, 3, 4, 5 (Box 79, Folder 756)
  - TCSCM: Chapter 5 (Box 79, Folder 757)
  - TCSCM: Chapter 6 (Box 79, Folder 758)
  - TCSCM: Chapter 7 (Box 79, Folder 759)
  - TCSCM: Chapter 8 (Box 80, Folder 760)
  - TCSCM: Chapter 9 (Box 80, Folder 761)
  - TCSCM: Chapter 10 (Box 80, Folder 762)
  - TCSCM: Chapters 10, 11 (Box 80, Folder 763)
  - TCSCM: Chapters 12, 13 (Box 80, Folder 764)
  - TCSCM: Chapter 14 (Box 80, Folder 765)
  - TCSCM: Chapters 15, 16 (Box 80, Folder 766)
  - TCSCM: Chapters 16, 17 (Box 80, Folder 767)
  - TCSCM: Chapter 18 (Box 80, Folder 768)
  - TCSCM: Chapter 19; re. J.R. Mott (Box 80, Folder 769)
  - TCSCM: Chapter 20 (Box 80a, Folder 770)
  - TCSCM: Chapter 21 (Box 80a, Folder 771)
  - TCSCM: Chapters 22, 23 (Box 80a, Folder 772a)
  - TCSCM: Chapter 24 (Box 80a, Folder 772b)
  - TCSCM: unidentified drafts (Box 80a, Folder 772c)
  - Unitarian Student Work (Box 80a, Folder 772)
  - United Student Christian Council (Box 80a, Folder 772e)
  - United Student Christian Council (Box 80a, Folder 772)
  - United Student Christian Movement (Box 80a, Folder 772g)
  - University Case Studies (Box 80a, Folder 772h)
  - University Christian Associations (Box 81, Folder 773)
  - The University Christian Movement (Box 81, Folder 774)
  - The University Religious Conference (Box 81, Folder 775)
  - Urban Universities (Box 81, Folder 776)
  - Urban Universities (Box 81, Folder 777)
  - Women in Higher Education (Box 81, Folder 778)
  - Women in Higher Education (Box 81, Folder 779)
  - Women in Higher Education (Box 81, Folder 780)
  - Women Students at Y.D.S. (Box 81, Folder 781)
  - World Student Christian Federation (Box 81, Folder 782)
  - World Student Christian Federation (Box 81, Folder 783)
  - World Student Christian Federation - (card file) (Box 82, Folder 784)
  - World War II: American education during war-time (newspaper clippings) (Box 83, Folder 785)
  - World War II: American education during war-time (newspaper clippings) (Box 83, Folder 786)
  - World War II: American education during war-time (newspaper clippings) (Box 83, Folder 787)
  - World War II: American education during war-time (newspaper clippings) (Box 83, Folder 788)
  - World War II: Anti-war movements (Box 83, Folder 789)
  - World War II: Effect of war on higher education (Box 83, Folder 790)
  - World War II: Effect of war on teaching of religion in colleges (Box 83, Folder 791)
  - World War II: Post-War higher education (Box 84, Folder 792)
  - World War II: Relation of Y.M.C.A. to military (Box 84, Folder 793)
  - World War II: Religion in Post-War Higher Education (Box 84, Folder 794)
  - World War II: Religious Program for Student Trainees (Box 84, Folder 795)
  - World War II: Religious Program for Student Trainees (Box 84, Folder 796)
  - World War II: Religious Program for Student Trainees (Box 84, Folder 797)
  - World War II: Religious Program for Student Trainees (Box 84, Folder 798)
  - World War II: Religious Program for Student Trainees (Box 84, Folder 799)
  - World War II: Religious Program for Student Trainees (Box 84, Folder 800)
  - War Emergency Council; agendas of meetings (Box 85, Folder 801)
  - War Emergency Council; consultative conferences (Box 85, Folder 802)
  - War Emergency Council; correspondence (Box 85, Folder 803)
  - War Emergency Council; literature for student trainees (Box 85, Folder 804)
  - War Emergency Council; minutes of meetings (Box 85, Folder 805)
  - War Emergency Council; miscellaneous (Box 85, Folder 806)
  - War Emergency Council; miscellaneous (Box 85, Folder 807)
  - War Emergency Council; miscellaneous (Box 85, Folder 808)
  - War Emergency Council; New England area (Box 85, Folder 809)
  - War Emergency Council; Pacific Northwest area (Box 85, Folder 810)
  - War Emergency Council; resources for student work (Box 85, Folder 811)
  - War Emergency Council; Southern area (Box 86, Folder 812)
  - War Emergency Council; Southwest area (Box 86, Folder 813)
  - War-time college situation (Box 86, Folder 814)
  - War-time college situation (Box 86, Folder 815)
  - War-time college situation (Box 86, Folder 816)
  - Work with student trainees: Pacific Northwest Consultative Conference, 1943 (Box 86, Folder 817)
  - World's Committee (Box 86, Folder 817a)
  - Yale Christian Association Religion in Higher Education Program (see: Religion in Higher Education - Yale Program) (Box 86, Folder 818)
  - Yale Training for Y.M.C.A. Leadership Positions (Box 86, Folder 819)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Central Field (Box 86, Folder 820)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Commission on Advance Program Among Student Associations (Box 86, Folder 821)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Commission on the Message and Mission of the Student Y.M.C.A. (Box 86, Folder 822)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Commission on place and function of Christian Associations in present university situation (Box 86, Folder 823)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Commission on Student Work (Box 87, Folder 824)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Commission on the training of student secretaries (Box 87, Folder 825)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Committee of Four - relationship between student Y. and National Council (Box 87, Folder 826)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Committee of Four - relationship between student Y. and National Council (Box 87, Folder 827)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Committee of Four - relationship between student Y. and National Council (Box 87, Folder 828)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Committee on Historical Resources (Box 87, Folder 829)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Consultation on Health Phys. Ed., 1952 (Box 87, Folder 829a)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Contributions to Higher Education (Box 87, Folder 830)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Evaluative studies (Box 87, Folder 831)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Miscellaneous (Box 88, Folder 832)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Mission of the movement (Box 88, Folder 833)
  - Y.M.C.A.: New England area (Box 88, Folder 834)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Pacific Coast area (Box 88, Folder 835)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Personnel Study of Secretaries, 1930 (Box 88, Folder 836)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Personnel Study of Secretaries, 1930 (Box 88, Folder 837)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Personnel Study of Secretaries, 1930 (Box 88, Folder 838)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Personnel Study of Secretaries, 1930 (Box 89, Folder 839)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Personnel Study of Secretaries, 1930 (Box 89, Folder 840)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Personnel Study of Secretaries, 1931, 1934 (Box 89, Folder 841)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Personnel Study of Secretaries, 1950 (Box 89, Folder 842)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Relationships between student work and general movement (Box 89, Folder 843)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Relationships with other religious agencies (Box 89, Folder 844)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Rocky Mountain Region (Box 89, Folder 845)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Study of relation of student Y.M.C.A. to university situation, 1924 (Box 89, Folder 846)
  - Y.M.C.A.: Supervision of Student Associations (Box 89, Folder 847)
  - Y.M.C.A.: World's Committee Staff Mtg. Minutes 1953 (Box 89, Folder 847)
  - Y.M.C.A. - History, Shedd exams (Box 89, Folder 848)
  - Y.W.C.A. (Box 89, Folder 849)